<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Atanas Yonkov</title>
    <link>https://yonkov.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Atanas Yonkov</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://yonkov.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my portfolio website! I am a blogger, web developer and an avid dreamer. I live in Bulgaria. In my free time I enjoy playing the guitar and hiking. I am very passionate about web development. I work as a freelancer and web developer. I am always interested in joining in new projects. Feel free to drop me a line if you have an interesting idea and we can start working on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Excel Formulas You Should Start Using Now</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/20-excel-formulas-you-should-start-using-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/20-excel-formulas-you-should-start-using-now/</guid>
      <description>MS Excel is one of the most popular data analysis tools in the world. More and more companies greatly depend on this software and quite a lot of people are using it on a daily basis. However, from my experience, not many are taking full advantage of the opportunities that the program can offer. Here is my list of the 20 most important Excel functions, which everyone should use in order to increase his efficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make a Website from Scratch Using PHP and MYSQL</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-make-a-website-from-scratch-using-php-and-mysql/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 19:48:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-make-a-website-from-scratch-using-php-and-mysql/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, I am going to teach you how to create a dynamic website from scratch using PHP 7 and Mysql. This article is a nice real-life example that can help beginner learners to understand the basics of PHP and MYSQL. It is written for educational purposes, however, it represents a good base that can be used to deliver a fully-operational digital product. Together, we shall create an example website with login and registration form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Awesome Things You Can Do with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/4-awesome-things-you-can-do-with-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 21:23:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/4-awesome-things-you-can-do-with-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Hugo is an awesome static website generator, which you can use to create portfolio websites and blogs. So, what makes Hugo so great?
Speed Hugo is absurdly fast! The Developers claim that a webpage can render just for 1 milisecond!
Functionalities 
1. Create a list page or a post using default templates.
2. Shortcodes
You can use a shortcode instead of custom HTML to embed an youtube video. Just like that:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Application Development</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/service/service4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 21:23:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/service/service4/</guid>
      <description>Web development with Wordpress. Experience with portfolio websites, ecommerce websites, forums and blogs. “Mobile first” responsive design approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Website Maintenance</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/service/service1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 21:23:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/service/service1/</guid>
      <description>Webmaster services and Web Support. Experience with portfolio websites, ecommerce websites, forums and blogs. “Mobile first” responsive design approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Web Design</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/service/service3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 21:23:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/service/service3/</guid>
      <description>Web development with Wordpress. Experience with portfolio websites, ecommerce websites, forums and blogs. “Mobile first” responsive design approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wordpress integration</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/service/service2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/service/service2/</guid>
      <description>Integration of existing websites to Wordpress. Experience with portfolio websites, ecommerce websites, forums and blogs. “Mobile first” responsive design approach.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>