<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Atanas Yonkov</title>
    <link>https://yonkov.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Atanas Yonkov</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 18:47:58 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://yonkov.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my portfolio website! I am a blogger, web developer and an avid dreamer. I live in Bulgaria. In my free time I enjoy playing the guitar and hiking. I am very passionate about web development. I work as a freelancer and web developer. I am always interested in joining in new projects. Feel free to drop me a line if you have an interesting idea and we can start working on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>If you require any more information or have any questions about this website&amp;rsquo;s privacy policy, please feel free to contact me by email at yonkov.atanas@gmail.com.
This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information is collected and recorded by yonkov.github.io and how it is used.
Log Files Yonkov.github.io is a static website and as such it does not require or store log files
Cookies and Web Beacons Yonkov.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12 Custom WooCommerce Functions That Will Make You Stand Out</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/12-custom-woocommerce-functions-that-will-make-you-stand-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 18:47:58 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/12-custom-woocommerce-functions-that-will-make-you-stand-out/</guid>
      <description>WooCommerce is the most popular ecommerce platform in the world and there is a reason for this – it is highly customizable, easy to use and completely free. While it gives you an awesome standardized solution, which you may use to build a complete online store, sometimes you may want to expand your Wordpress website functionalities and further customize it according to your clients’ needs. In this way, you can make your website stand out from the rest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Change Product Title Based on Variations WooCommerce</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/change-product-title-based-on-product-variations-in-woocommerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 18:35:21 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/change-product-title-based-on-product-variations-in-woocommerce/</guid>
      <description>WooCommerce is an awesome e-commerce plugin that you can use to create beautiful ecommerce stores. However, sometimes you may also need to customise or change its functionalities, based on your customer’s specific requirements. Luckily, WooCommerce is a highly customizable Wordpress plugin. You can use the provided actions to give your clients the best user experience possible.
The default WooCommerce behaviour does not allow you to change the page title on the single product page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Customize a Very Long Drop Down Menu in Divi</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-style-a-very-long-drop-down-menu-in-divi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 17:53:08 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-style-a-very-long-drop-down-menu-in-divi/</guid>
      <description>How to fix the issue with long drop-downs in Wordpress? This is a common question when you have a main menu item with many sub items. You usually come to a point when the content can go below the fold of the screen. In these cases, you will not be able to see the remaining submenu items. Luckily to all of us who are using the Divi theme, there is a nice hidden feature, called &amp;ldquo;mega menu&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Change the Color of the “Add to Cart” button in Divi</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-change-the-color-of-woocommerce-add-to-cart-button-in-divi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 17:08:06 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-change-the-color-of-woocommerce-add-to-cart-button-in-divi/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, I am going to show you how to change the style of the “Add to Cart” button in your Divi theme. The Woocommerce &amp;ldquo;Add to Cart&amp;rdquo; button is the first thing that the customer sees on your product page, so it is really important to style it with a color that corresponds well with your theme. After all, you do not want to lose sales because your website design is not as good as your competitors’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>18 ready-to-use VBA Codes that will save your day</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/18-ready-to-use-vba-codes-that-will-save-your-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 21:02:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/18-ready-to-use-vba-codes-that-will-save-your-day/</guid>
      <description>In this article, I am going to show you some of the most amazing VBA Excel codes that you can use to optimize your work. VBA is a programming language, which can be used to extend the capabilities of MS Excel and other MS Office applications. It is extremely helpful for MS Excel users, because it can be used to automate your work and significantly improve your efficiency. This article will introduce you to VBA and show you some of the most useful, ready to use VBA codes out there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Set up Static IP in Windows XP and Windows 7</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-set-up-static-ip-in-windows-xp-and-windows-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 15:24:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-set-up-static-ip-in-windows-xp-and-windows-7/</guid>
      <description>Static IP means that your computer is assigned an IP address that does not change each time the PC is restarted. It is required in some situations, for example, to access an ftp server or a web server from another computer inside the network. To do this, you need to change the IP version 4 (TCP / IP) properties. First, go to the start menu and type cmd in the search bar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Excel Formulas You Should Start Using Now</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/20-excel-formulas-you-should-start-using-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/20-excel-formulas-you-should-start-using-now/</guid>
      <description>MS Excel is one of the most popular data analysis tools in the world. More and more companies greatly depend on this software and quite a lot of people are using it on a daily basis. However, from my experience, not many are taking full advantage of the opportunities that the program can offer. Here is my list of the top 20 most important Excel functions, which everyone should use in order to increase his efficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make a Website from Scratch Using PHP and MYSQL</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-make-a-website-from-scratch-using-php-and-mysql/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 19:48:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-make-a-website-from-scratch-using-php-and-mysql/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, I am going to teach you how to create a dynamic website from scratch using PHP 7 and Mysql. This article is a nice real-life example that can help beginner learners to understand the basics of PHP and MYSQL. It is written for educational purposes, however, it represents a good base that can be used to deliver a fully-operational digital product. Together, we shall create an example website with login and registration form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Awesome Things You Can Do with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/4-awesome-things-you-can-do-with-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 21:23:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/4-awesome-things-you-can-do-with-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Hugo is an awesome static website generator, which you can use to create beautiful portfolio websites and blogs. So, what makes Hugo so great?
Speed Hugo is absurdly fast! The Developers claim that a webpage can render just for 1 milisecond!
Functionalities 1. Create a list page or a post using default templates.
There are two types of templates you can use in Hugo. These are the single page templates and list page templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Application Development</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/service/service4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 21:23:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/service/service4/</guid>
      <description>Web development with Wordpress. Experience with portfolio websites, ecommerce websites, forums and blogs. “Mobile first” responsive design approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Website Maintenance</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/service/service1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 21:23:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/service/service1/</guid>
      <description>Webmaster services and Web Support. Experience with portfolio websites, ecommerce websites, forums and blogs. “Mobile first” responsive design approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Website Maintenance</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/subheader/subheader/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 21:23:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/subheader/subheader/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my professional website! I work as a devoted web developer and a freelancer. My ultimate goal is customer satisfaction. I focus on quality and creating value for my clients.   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Web Design</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/service/service3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 21:23:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/service/service3/</guid>
      <description>Web development with Wordpress. Experience with portfolio websites, ecommerce websites, forums and blogs. “Mobile first” responsive design approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wordpress integration</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/service/service2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 21:23:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/service/service2/</guid>
      <description>Integration of existing websites to Wordpress. Experience with portfolio websites, ecommerce websites, forums and blogs. “Mobile first” responsive design approach.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>