<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Excel on Atanas Yonkov</title>
    <link>https://yonkov.github.io/categories/excel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Excel on Atanas Yonkov</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 21:02:46 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://yonkov.github.io/categories/excel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Remove Top Menu Transition Effect in Divi</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-remove-top-menu-transition-effect-in-divi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 21:02:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-remove-top-menu-transition-effect-in-divi/</guid>
      <description>The Divi theme is one of the most versatile WordPress premium themes with tons of options that also comes together with its powerful page builder. However, in some cases, you want to make some customizations and you simply cannot find a quick fix for them. An example for that is the Divi menu animation. The header always shrinks on page dropdown and while some may argue that this gives a modern feel to your Divi website, this transition effect is certainly not for everyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>18 ready-to-use VBA Codes that will save your day</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/18-ready-to-use-vba-codes-that-will-save-your-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 21:02:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/18-ready-to-use-vba-codes-that-will-save-your-day/</guid>
      <description>In this article, I am going to show you some of the most amazing VBA Excel codes that you can use to optimize your work. VBA is a programming language, which can be used to extend the capabilities of MS Excel and other MS Office applications. It is extremely helpful for MS Excel users, because it can be used to automate your work and significantly improve your efficiency. This article will introduce you to VBA and show you some of the most useful, ready to use VBA codes out there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Excel Formulas You Should Start Using Now</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/20-excel-formulas-you-should-start-using-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/20-excel-formulas-you-should-start-using-now/</guid>
      <description>MS Excel is one of the most popular data analysis tools in the world. More and more companies greatly depend on this software and quite a lot of people are using it on a daily basis. However, from my experience, not many are taking full advantage of the opportunities that the program can offer. Here is my list of the top 20 most important and useful Excel functions, which everyone should use in order to increase his efficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>