<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>_index on Atanas Yonkov</title>
    <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in _index on Atanas Yonkov</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 23:26:42 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://yonkov.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up Vuepress With Netlify CMS</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/setting-up-vuepress-with-netlify-cms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2019 10:05:06 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/setting-up-vuepress-with-netlify-cms/</guid>
      <description>Example website: https://github.com/yonkov/Vuepress-project
VuePress is one of the most promising frameworks to create extremely fast and lightweight static websites that act as Single page applications. By the end of this tutorial, you will have set up VuePress and added a light-weight and easy to use content management system, called Netlify CMS, designed specifically for static websites.
Let&amp;rsquo;s get started!
Table of Contents     The Rise of Static Site Generators Why VuePress Why Netlify CMS How to Install VuePress Add VuePress to Github Deploy to Netlify Integrate Netlify CMS to VuePress     The Rise of Static Site Generators Static site generators are becoming more and more popular these days due to better performance, low cost, high security and a better developer experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Display Cookie Notice in Your Divi Theme</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/display-cookie-notification-in-your-divi-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 14:04:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/display-cookie-notification-in-your-divi-theme/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, I will show you how to easily add a cookie notification popup to your Divi website. By the end of it, you will be able to display a cookie message on page load just the way I show it on my website. Now, let&amp;rsquo;s get on with it.    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});  Why do you need cookie consent?
Cookie consent is required by European Union&amp;rsquo;s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and ePrivacy Directive (ePR).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy Way to Add a Cookie Popup in WordPress Without a Plugin</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/easy-way-to-add-a-cookie-popup-in-wordpress-without-a-plugin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 15:24:12 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/easy-way-to-add-a-cookie-popup-in-wordpress-without-a-plugin/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial I am going to show you how to easily add a cookie notification popup to a WordPress website without installing any additional plugins.
Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong – I like plugins and I use a few of them on my websites. They are one of the main reasons that made WordPress so popular in the first place. With a simple click you can extend your website&amp;rsquo;s functionalities and give an easy answer to a complex technical problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Remove Top Menu Transition Effect in Divi</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-remove-top-menu-transition-effect-in-divi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 21:02:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-remove-top-menu-transition-effect-in-divi/</guid>
      <description>The Divi theme is one of the most versatile WordPress premium themes with tons of options that also comes together with its powerful page builder. However, in some cases, you want to make some customizations and you simply cannot find a quick fix for them. An example for that is the Divi menu animation. The header always shrinks on page dropdown and while some may argue that this gives a modern feel to your Divi website, this transition effect is certainly not for everyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy Way to Add Knowledge Graph to WordPress Without a Plugin</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/easy-way-to-add-knowledge-graph-to-wordpress-without-a-plugin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 17:08:06 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/easy-way-to-add-knowledge-graph-to-wordpress-without-a-plugin/</guid>
      <description>In this article, I am going to show you how to easily add Knowledge Graph to WordPress manually (without the use of plugins)
The Google’s Knowledge Graph is the big block of information that appears on the right-hand side of Google’s search results. The Knowledge Graph contains relevant, context-specific information, regarding your search. For example, if you search for Pablo Picasso in Google, you will see images and information regarding the famous painter on the right-hand side of your screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Convert Your Wordpress Site to Hugo</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-convert-your-wordpress-site-to-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 12:13:23 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-convert-your-wordpress-site-to-hugo/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, I am going to show you the things that I did to successfully migrate my WordPress website to Hugo static site generator.
Why would like to convert your WordPress website to Hugo?
WordPress is the most popular framework fo building websites. This is because it is open-source, it has user-friendly CMS, allows for customization and has tons of documentation online. However, sometimes you do not need a dynamic website with a database.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Change the Color of the Cart Icon in Divi</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-change-the-color-of-the-cart-icon-in-divi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 17:08:06 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-change-the-color-of-the-cart-icon-in-divi/</guid>
      <description>In this article, I am going to teach you how to change the color of the WooCommerce shopping cart icon in Divi. By default, the cart icon appears on your main menu bar after a successful Woocommerce installation. It is very important to style the cart icon in accordance with the other items from your primary menu, since it is one of the first things that the customer will see on your website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make a Mulilingual Website with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-make-a-mulilingual-website-with-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 21:02:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-make-a-mulilingual-website-with-hugo/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, I am going to show you how to create a multilingual website using Hugo. I am a big fan of Hugo, an awesome open-source static site generator with tons of cool features. It makes building websites fun again and it also supports multilingual mode. This means you can easily translate your Hugo website in any language you want! Follow me and I will teach you how to do it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12 Custom WooCommerce Functions That Will Make You Stand Out</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/12-custom-woocommerce-functions-that-will-make-you-stand-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 18:47:58 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/12-custom-woocommerce-functions-that-will-make-you-stand-out/</guid>
      <description>WooCommerce is the most popular ecommerce platform in the world and there is a reason for this – it is highly customizable, easy to use and completely free. While it gives you an awesome standardized solution, which you may use to build a complete online store, sometimes you may want to expand your Wordpress website functionalities and further customize it according to your clients’ needs. In this way, you can make your website stand out from the rest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Change Product Title Based on Variations WooCommerce</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/change-product-title-based-on-product-variations-in-woocommerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 18:35:21 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/change-product-title-based-on-product-variations-in-woocommerce/</guid>
      <description>WooCommerce is an awesome e-commerce plugin that you can use to create beautiful ecommerce stores. However, sometimes you may also need to customise or change its functionalities, based on your customer’s specific requirements. Luckily, WooCommerce is a highly customizable Wordpress plugin. You can use the provided actions to give your clients the best user experience possible.    (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});  The default WooCommerce behaviour does not allow you to change the page title on the single product page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Customize a Very Long Drop Down Menu in Divi</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-style-a-very-long-drop-down-menu-in-divi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 17:53:08 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-style-a-very-long-drop-down-menu-in-divi/</guid>
      <description>How to customize the drop down menu in your Divi theme? This is a common question when you have a menu item that is too long (has many submenu items). You usually come to a point when the content can go below the fold of the screen. In these cases, you will not be able to see the remaining submenu items. Luckily to all of us who are using the Divi theme, there is a nice hidden feature, called &amp;ldquo;mega menu&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Change the Color of the “Add to Cart” button in Divi</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-change-the-color-of-woocommerce-add-to-cart-button-in-divi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 17:08:06 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-change-the-color-of-woocommerce-add-to-cart-button-in-divi/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, I am going to show you how to change the style of the “Add to Cart” button in your Divi theme. The Woocommerce &amp;ldquo;Add to Cart&amp;rdquo; button is the first thing that the customer sees on your product page, so it is really important to style it with a color that corresponds well with your theme. After all, you do not want to lose sales because your website design is not as good as your competitors’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>18 ready-to-use VBA Codes that will save your day</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/18-ready-to-use-vba-codes-that-will-save-your-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 21:02:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/18-ready-to-use-vba-codes-that-will-save-your-day/</guid>
      <description>In this article, I am going to show you some of the most amazing VBA Excel codes that you can use to optimize your work. VBA is a programming language, which can be used to extend the capabilities of MS Excel and other MS Office applications. It is extremely helpful for MS Excel users, because it can be used to automate your work and significantly improve your efficiency. This article will introduce you to VBA and show you some of the most useful, ready to use VBA codes out there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Set up Static IP in Windows XP and Windows 7</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-set-up-static-ip-in-windows-xp-and-windows-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 15:24:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-set-up-static-ip-in-windows-xp-and-windows-7/</guid>
      <description>Static IP means that your computer is assigned an IP address that does not change each time the PC is restarted. It is required in some situations, for example, to access an ftp server or a web server from another computer inside the network. To do this, you need to change the IP version 4 (TCP / IP) properties. First, go to the start menu and type cmd in the search bar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Excel Formulas You Should Start Using Now</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/20-excel-formulas-you-should-start-using-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/20-excel-formulas-you-should-start-using-now/</guid>
      <description>MS Excel is one of the most popular data analysis tools in the world. More and more companies greatly depend on this software and quite a lot of people are using it on a daily basis. However, from my experience, not many are taking full advantage of the opportunities that the program can offer. Here is my list of the top 20 most important and useful Excel functions, which everyone should use in order to increase his efficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make a Website from Scratch Using PHP and MYSQL</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-make-a-website-from-scratch-using-php-and-mysql/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 19:48:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-make-a-website-from-scratch-using-php-and-mysql/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, I am going to teach you how to create a dynamic website from scratch using PHP 7 and Mysql. This article is a nice real-life example that can help beginner learners to understand the basics of PHP and MYSQL. It is written for educational purposes, however, it represents a good base that can be used to deliver a fully-operational digital product. Together, we shall create an example website with login and registration form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Reasons Why Hugo is Awesome</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/4-awesome-things-you-can-do-with-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 21:23:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/4-awesome-things-you-can-do-with-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Hugo is an awesome open-source static site generator, which you can use to create beautiful portfolio websites and blogs. Hugo started as a side project in 2013 and quickly became one of the most popular frameworks for building static websites. So, what are the ingredients that make Hugo so great? Here are the most important reasons why you should power your website with Hugo.
Speed Hugo is absurdly fast! The developers claim that one webpage can be built for less than 1 milisecond!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>