<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>_index on Atanas Yonkov</title>
    <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in _index on Atanas Yonkov</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 23:26:42 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://yonkov.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>18 ready-to-use VBA Codes that will save your day</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/18-ready-to-use-vba-codes-that-will-save-your-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 21:02:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/18-ready-to-use-vba-codes-that-will-save-your-day/</guid>
      <description>In this article, I am going to show you 18 amazing VBA codes that you can use to optimize your work. VBA is a programming language, which can be used to extend the capabilities of MS Excel and other MS Office applications. It is extremely helpful for MS Excel users, because it can be used to automate your work and significantly improve your efficiency. This article will introduce you to VBA and show you some of the most useful, ready to use VBA codes out there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Set up Static IP in Windows XP and Windows 7</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-set-up-static-ip-in-windows-xp-and-windows-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 15:24:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-set-up-static-ip-in-windows-xp-and-windows-7/</guid>
      <description>Static IP means that your computer is assigned an IP address that does not change each time the PC is restarted. It is required in some situations, for example, to access an ftp server or a web server from another computer inside the network. To do this, you need to change the IP version 4 (TCP / IP) properties. First, go to the start menu and type cmd in the search bar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Excel Formulas You Should Start Using Now</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/20-excel-formulas-you-should-start-using-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/20-excel-formulas-you-should-start-using-now/</guid>
      <description>MS Excel is one of the most popular data analysis tools in the world. More and more companies greatly depend on this software and quite a lot of people are using it on a daily basis. However, from my experience, not many are taking full advantage of the opportunities that the program can offer. Here is my list of the 20 most important Excel functions, which everyone should use in order to increase his efficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make a Website from Scratch Using PHP and MYSQL</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-make-a-website-from-scratch-using-php-and-mysql/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 19:48:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-make-a-website-from-scratch-using-php-and-mysql/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, I am going to teach you how to create a dynamic website from scratch using PHP 7 and Mysql. This article is a nice real-life example that can help beginner learners to understand the basics of PHP and MYSQL. It is written for educational purposes, however, it represents a good base that can be used to deliver a fully-operational digital product. Together, we shall create an example website with login and registration form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Awesome Things You Can Do with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/4-awesome-things-you-can-do-with-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 21:23:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/4-awesome-things-you-can-do-with-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Hugo is an awesome static website generator, which you can use to create beautiful portfolio websites and blogs. So, what makes Hugo so great?
Speed Hugo is absurdly fast! The Developers claim that a webpage can render just for 1 milisecond!
Functionalities 1. Create a list page or a post using default templates.
There are two types of templates you can use in Hugo. These are the single page templates and list page templates.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>