<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hugo on Atanas Yonkov</title>
    <link>https://yonkov.github.io/categories/hugo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hugo on Atanas Yonkov</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 11:49:32 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://yonkov.github.io/categories/hugo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Switching off the Lights Part Two - Adding Dark Mode to Hugo</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/add-dark-mode-toggle-to-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 11:49:32 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/add-dark-mode-toggle-to-hugo/</guid>
      <description>In my last blog post, I wrote about how to Add Dark Mode Toggle to WordPress. Today I will go a step further, by showing you how to switch between light and dark (day and night) theme mode in Hugo - the fastest framework for creating static web sites. This time, we will make a dark theme toggle button similar to what Redux author and React pioneer Dan Abramov did in his open-source blog Overreacted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Convert Your Wordpress Site to Hugo</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-convert-your-wordpress-site-to-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 12:13:23 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-convert-your-wordpress-site-to-hugo/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, I am going to show you the things that I did to successfully migrate my WordPress website to Hugo static site generator.
Why would like to convert your WordPress website to Hugo?
WordPress is the most popular framework fo building websites. This is because it is open-source, it has user-friendly CMS, allows for customization and has tons of documentation online. However, sometimes you do not need a dynamic website with a database.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make a Multilingual Website with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-make-a-mulilingual-website-with-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 21:02:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-make-a-mulilingual-website-with-hugo/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, I am going to show you how to create a multilanguage website using Hugo. I am a big fan of Hugo, an awesome open-source static site generator with tons of cool features. It makes building websites fun again and it also supports multilingual mode. This means you can easily translate your Hugo website in any language you want! Follow me and I will teach you how to do it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Reasons Why Hugo is Awesome</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/4-awesome-things-you-can-do-with-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 21:23:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/4-awesome-things-you-can-do-with-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Hugo is an awesome open-source static site generator, which you can use to create beautiful portfolio websites and blogs. Hugo started as a side project in 2013 and quickly became one of the most popular frameworks for building static websites. In fact, this website is also built with Hugo! So, what are the ingredients that make Hugo so great? Here are the most important reasons why you should power your website with Hugo.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>