<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dark Mode on Atanas Yonkov</title>
    <link>https://yonkov.github.io/tags/dark-mode/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dark Mode on Atanas Yonkov</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 11:49:32 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://yonkov.github.io/tags/dark-mode/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Switching off the Lights Part Three - Adding Dark Mode to VuePress</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/add-dark-mode-to-vuepress/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 11:49:32 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/add-dark-mode-to-vuepress/</guid>
      <description>Dark mode is one of the newest and hottest trends in web development. Since release of macOS 10.14 in September 2018, more and more apps are starting to offer the option for users to choose a dark system-wide interface over the standard light color scheme. Recent versions of Windows 10 and Android also started to offer dark mode layout. It is perceived that a dark background is much more easier on the eyes and attracts more readers, especially during night time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Switching off the Lights Part Two - Adding Dark Mode to Hugo</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/add-dark-mode-toggle-to-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 11:49:32 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/add-dark-mode-toggle-to-hugo/</guid>
      <description>In my last blog post, I wrote about how to Add Dark Mode Toggle to WordPress. Today I will go a step further, by showing you how to switch between light and dark (day and night) theme mode in Hugo - the fastest framework for creating static web sites. This time, we will make a dark theme toggle button similar to what Redux author and React pioneer Dan Abramov did in his open-source blog Overreacted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Switching off the Lights - Adding Dark Mode to WordPress</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/add-dark-mode-toggle-button-to-wordpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 17:46:43 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/add-dark-mode-toggle-button-to-wordpress/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, 30 March, StackOverflow started to offer a dark theme version (still in beta) for their visitors. On their home page, you can read:
 &amp;ldquo;You’ve been asking for dark mode for years. The dark mode beta is finally here. Change your preferences any time.&amp;rdquo;
 More and More web apps are offering or considering to offer a &amp;ldquo;dark mode&amp;rdquo; layout to their visitors that comes together with their normal, &amp;ldquo;light mode&amp;rdquo; layout.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>