<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shepherd on Atanas Yonkov</title>
    <link>https://yonkov.github.io/categories/shepherd/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Shepherd on Atanas Yonkov</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 20:57:49 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://yonkov.github.io/categories/shepherd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Add a Progress Bar in Shepherd.js</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/progress-bar-in-shepherd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 20:57:49 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/progress-bar-in-shepherd/</guid>
      <description>Shepherd.js is an easy to use interactive onboarding user guide that can help visitors throughout the content of the app. This is very useful if you want to show your users around, focus on your product&amp;rsquo;s strengths or just help the others navigate in your app more easily. Shepherd.js is an open source software that I highly recommend, because it is easy to use, has great documentation, friendly support team and most importantly - it can improve user experience and help your site convert more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Ways to Add a Tour Guide in WordPress (With and Without a Plugin)</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/create-tour-guide-in-wordpress-with-shepherd.js/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 19:17:04 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/create-tour-guide-in-wordpress-with-shepherd.js/</guid>
      <description>Why is User Onboarding Important? Guided tours matter. In fact, if you are still not using interactive user introductions to guide users throughout your app&amp;rsquo;s content, you should probably start doing that as soon as possible. Let me tell you why. When the user visits a web page for a first time, he probably arrived there because he was searching for something in the first place and he might or might not figure out where to look for it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>