<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wordpress on Atanas Yonkov</title>
    <link>https://yonkov.github.io/categories/wordpress/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Wordpress on Atanas Yonkov</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 17:08:06 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://yonkov.github.io/categories/wordpress/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy Way to Add Knowledge Graph to WordPress Without a Plugin</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/easy-way-to-add-knowledge-graph-to-wordpress-without-a-plugin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 17:08:06 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/easy-way-to-add-knowledge-graph-to-wordpress-without-a-plugin/</guid>
      <description>In this article, I am going to show you how to easily add Knowledge Graph to WordPress manually (without the use of plugins)
The Google’s Knowledge Graph is the big block of information that appears on the right-hand side of Google’s search results. The Knowledge Graph contains relevant, context-specific information, regarding your search. For example, if you search for Pablo Picasso in Google, you will see images and information regarding the famous painter on the right-hand side of your screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Change the Color of the Cart Icon in Divi</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-change-the-color-of-the-cart-icon-in-divi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 17:08:06 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-change-the-color-of-the-cart-icon-in-divi/</guid>
      <description>In this article, I am going to teach you how to change the color of the WooCommerce shopping cart icon in Divi. By default, the cart icon appears on your main menu bar after a successful Woocommerce installation. It is very important to style the cart icon in accordance with the other items from your primary menu, since it is one of the first things that the customer will see on your website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12 Custom WooCommerce Functions That Will Make You Stand Out</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/12-custom-woocommerce-functions-that-will-make-you-stand-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 18:47:58 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/12-custom-woocommerce-functions-that-will-make-you-stand-out/</guid>
      <description>WooCommerce is the most popular ecommerce platform in the world and there is a reason for this – it is highly customizable, easy to use and completely free. While it gives you an awesome standardized solution, which you may use to build a complete online store, sometimes you may want to expand your Wordpress website functionalities and further customize it according to your clients’ needs. In this way, you can make your website stand out from the rest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Change Product Title Based on Variations WooCommerce</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/change-product-title-based-on-product-variations-in-woocommerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 18:35:21 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/change-product-title-based-on-product-variations-in-woocommerce/</guid>
      <description>WooCommerce is an awesome e-commerce plugin that you can use to create beautiful ecommerce stores. However, sometimes you may also need to customise or change its functionalities, based on your customer’s specific requirements. Luckily, WooCommerce is a highly customizable Wordpress plugin. You can use the provided actions to give your clients the best user experience possible.
The default WooCommerce behaviour does not allow you to change the page title on the single product page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Customize a Very Long Drop Down Menu in Divi</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-style-a-very-long-drop-down-menu-in-divi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 17:53:08 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-style-a-very-long-drop-down-menu-in-divi/</guid>
      <description>How to fix the issue with long drop-downs in Wordpress? This is a common question when you have a main menu item with many sub items. You usually come to a point when the content can go below the fold of the screen. In these cases, you will not be able to see the remaining submenu items. Luckily to all of us who are using the Divi theme, there is a nice hidden feature, called &amp;ldquo;mega menu&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Change the Color of the “Add to Cart” button in Divi</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-change-the-color-of-woocommerce-add-to-cart-button-in-divi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 17:08:06 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/how-to-change-the-color-of-woocommerce-add-to-cart-button-in-divi/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, I am going to show you how to change the style of the “Add to Cart” button in your Divi theme. The Woocommerce &amp;ldquo;Add to Cart&amp;rdquo; button is the first thing that the customer sees on your product page, so it is really important to style it with a color that corresponds well with your theme. After all, you do not want to lose sales because your website design is not as good as your competitors’.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>