<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vuepress on Atanas Yonkov</title>
    <link>https://yonkov.github.io/categories/vuepress/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Vuepress on Atanas Yonkov</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 11:49:32 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://yonkov.github.io/categories/vuepress/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Switching off the Lights Part Three - Adding Dark Mode to VuePress</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/add-dark-mode-to-vuepress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 11:49:32 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/add-dark-mode-to-vuepress/</guid>
      <description>Dark mode is one of the newest and hottest trends in web development. Since release of macOS 10.14 in September 2018, more and more apps are starting to offer the option for users to choose a dark system-wide interface over the standard light color scheme. Recent versions of Windows 10 and Android also started to offer dark mode layout. It is perceived that a dark background is much more easier on the eyes and attracts more readers, especially during night time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up Vuepress With Netlify CMS</title>
      <link>https://yonkov.github.io/post/setting-up-vuepress-with-netlify-cms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2019 10:05:06 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yonkov.github.io/post/setting-up-vuepress-with-netlify-cms/</guid>
      <description>Example repo: https://github.com/yonkov/Vuepress-project
VuePress is one of the most promising frameworks to create extremely fast and lightweight static websites that act as single page applications. By the end of this tutorial, you will know how to set up VuePress and add a light-weight and easy to use content management system to it, called Netlify CMS.
Let&amp;rsquo;s get started!
Table of Contents     The Rise of Static Site Generators Why VuePress Why Netlify CMS How to Install VuePress Add VuePress to Github Deploy to Netlify Integrate Netlify CMS to VuePress     The Rise of Static Site Generators Static site generators are becoming more and more popular these days due to better performance, low cost, high security and better developer experience.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>